Ashish Paul

I am a Front-end developer with 1 & Half years experiences and was an IT Technician with 8+ years of experiences. I am Looking for a challenging role in a reputable organization to utilize my technical skills for the growth of the organization as well as to enhance my knowledge about new and emerging trends in the IT sector.



- 🧕 MAA Durga Road, Sripuria Tingrai Habi, Near Durga Mandir, Tinsukia, Assam, India, Pin-786125 🛭 & <u>8473073314</u>
- ashishpaul674@gmail.com
 https://ashish-paul-portfolio.netlify.app/
- in Ashish Paul 🗶 ashish674paul

Experience

Much More

IT Technician

Tinsukia, Assam, India

2021-01-11 to 2022-05-14

- Software Installation & Configuration.
- Hardware Installation, Diagnosis & Maintenance.
- IP Cameras, Switches, Routers Configuration & Installation.
- Remote Support(Via:-Team Viewer & Any Desk).

Shiksha Valley School

IT Assistant

Dibrugarh, Assam, India

2018-09-11 to 2020-09-19

- Software Installation & Configuration.
- Smart Board, Laptop & Desktop Installation, Diagnosis & Maintenance.
- IP Cameras, Switches, Routers & RFID (Radio Frequency Identification Device) Systems Configuration & Installation.
- Cloud Software(Cloud9)
- https://www.shikshavalleyschool.org/

Much More

IT Technician

Tinsukia, Assam

2014-09-01 to 2018-08-30

- Software Installation & Configuration.
- Hardware Installation, Diagnosis & Maintenance.
- IP Cameras, Switches, Routers Configuration & Installation.
- Remote Support(Via:-Team Viewer & Any Desk).

CAS Computers

Computer Technician

Tinsukia, Assam

2013-01-02 to 2014-08-31

- $\bullet \quad \hbox{Software Installation \& Configuration.}$
- Hardware Installation, Diagnosis & Maintenance.
- IP Cameras, Switches, Routers Configuration & Installation

Interests

Listening Music

Traveling

Watching Online Videos, Movies

YouTube

Bike Riding

Learning New Skills

Languages

Bengali

Native



Hindi



Assamese

10



Skills

Desktop & Laptop (Hardware)

9 yrs exp in Hardware Installation & Diagnosis

Installation, Diagnosis, Maintenance, Repairing

Software

& etc) installation & configuration and cloude software(like: cloud9 by shauryasoft)

9 yrs exp in software (like: operating system, MS office

Operation System, Office, Cloud Software, Installation,

Configuration

Networking

7 yrs exp in networking



RFID Systems, Router & Switches Configuration & Maintenance, Cameras Configuration & Maintenance, Printers & Systems sharing in network, IP Configuration

Education

Udemy

Full Stack Web Development

Web Development

2022-03-19

- Front-End Web Development:- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JS ES6, DOM, JQuery, Unix Command Line.
- Back-end Web Development: Node.js, APIs, Git & Github, EJS, Databases, SQL, MongoDB, Mongoose, React.js, Web3, DApp - BBANK, ICP Live Blockchain, Minting NFTs and Building an NFT Marketplace.
- https://www.udemy.com/

Tinsukia College

Commerce (Class XI & XII) 36%

Higher Secondary(AHSEC)

2009-06-02 to 2012-06-04

- Accountancy
- MIL(Bengali)
- Business Studies
- English
- Commercial Arithmetic & elements of Statistics
- Banking
- https://tinsukiacollege.in/

Tinsukia Railway High School

Class V to X

50%

School (H.S.L.C.)

2002-01-03 to 2009-05-29

Certifications

ACA

Academy of Computer Accountant

2011-07-02

- Microsoft Office.
- Operating System (Windows, Ubuntu)
- C++
- HTML

NIIT

NIIT Accademy

2014-04-18

Protocols & Inter-networking Standards (N+)

https://www.niit.com/india/

NIIT

NIIT Accademy

2013-05-24

Certificate Course In PC Technician A+

https://www.niit.com/india/